digiuniv.com 2018-01-08

# Learning Management System | University Management System | Campus Management System

###  Disclaimer

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by Digunivand while we endeavor to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Diguniv uses and protects any information that you give Digunivwhen you use this website. 

Diguniv committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement? 

### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Digiuniv uses cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. No personal information will be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

### Securitys

Digiuniv has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

### Refund Policy

All Transactions are final with no refund or exchange permitted. You are responsible for the Fee payment. Digiuniv is not responsible for any fee payment which is done for incorrect account. However, if in a transaction performed by you on the Site, money has been charged to your card or bank account and a Recharge is not delivered within 24 hours of your completion of the transaction then you ay inform us by sending an email to our customer services email address mentioned on the Contact Us page. Please include in the email the following details –Course, Student Detail,   
Transaction date and Order Number. Digiuniv shall investigate the incident and if it is found that money was indeed charged to your card or bank account without delivery of the fee payment then you will be refunded the money within 10 working days from the date of receipt of your email. All Refunds will be credited on the same account.
